Guide to the Ann Cornelisen Papers, 1714-1994 (bulk 1954-1990)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IV Photographs
  - Prints
    - Professional
      - "Roccanova" - Miscellaneous (11.25)
      - "Salandra, Matera,", 1956 (11.26)
      - "Scandale, Calabria,", 1960 (11.27)
      - "Scandale, Calabria,", 1960 (11.28)
      - "Scandale, Calabria,", 1960 (11.29)
      - "Scandale, Calabria,", 1960 (11.30)
      - "Scandale, Calabria,", 1960 (11.31)
      - San Pietro Avellana, circa 1956 (11.32)
      - "Stigliano-Aliano-Alianello" (11.33)
      - "Stigliano-Aliano-Alianello" (11.34)
      - "Stigliano-Aliano-Alianello" (11.35)
      - "Stigliano-Aliano-Alianello" (11.36)
      - "Stigliano-Aliano-Alianello" (11.37)
      - "Stigliano-Aliano-Alianello" (11.38)
      - San Nicola, San Giorgio, Ortona, et al – Blizzard, Feb - Mar 1956 (11.39)
      - San Nicola, San Giorgio, Ortona, et al - Blizzard (11.40)
      - Tolve, Potenza - San Rocco, 1966 (9.5)
      - Fortnightly Club Lecture photos, compiled in Feb 1958, nos. 2 - 10 (8.25)
      - Fortnightly Club Lecture photos, compiled in Feb 1958, nos. 11-19 (8.26)
      - Fortnightly Club Lecture photos, compiled in Feb 1958, nos. 20-26 (8.27)
      - Fortnightly Club Lecture photos, compiled in Feb 1958, nos. 27-32 (8.28)
      - Miscellaneous - Save the Children Fund Nursery, 1962, n.d. (9.6)
      - Miscellaneous - Save the Children Fund? (12.1)
      - Miscellaneous - Landscapes (9.7)
      - Miscellaneous - "Children" (9.8)
      - Miscellaneous - Children (12.2)
      - Miscellaneous - Children (12.3)
      - Miscellaneous - Children (12.4)
      - Miscellaneous - Children (12.5)
      - Miscellaneous - "Men" (9.9)
      - Miscellaneous - "Women" (9.10)
      - Miscellaneous - Mausoleum (12.6)
      - Miscellaneous - Funeral (12.7)
      - Miscellaneous - Nuns (12.8)
      - Miscellaneous – Wedding, 1974 (12.9)
      - Miscellaneous - Sitters - Women (12.10)
      - Miscellaneous - Sitters - Women (12.11)
      - Miscellaneous - Sitters - Men (12.12)
      - Miscellaneous - Groups of Women (12.13)
      - Miscellaneous - Groups of Women (12.14)
      - Miscellaneous - Portraits (12.15)
      - Miscellaneous - Portraits (12.16)
      - Miscellaneous - Laundry (12.17)
      - Miscellaneous - Farming (12.18)
      - Miscellaneous - Farming (12.19)
      - Miscellaneous - Farming (12.20)
      - Miscellaneous - Farming (12.21)
      - Miscellaneous - Farming (12.22)
      - Miscellaneous - Farming (12.23)
      - Miscellaneous - Farming (12.24)
      - Miscellaneous - Farming (12.25)
      - Miscellaneous - Markets (12.26)
      - Miscellaneous - Markets (12.27)
      - Miscellaneous - Transport (12.28)
      - Miscellaneous - Transport (12.29)
      - Miscellaneous - Rainy Streets (13.1)
      - Miscellaneous - Rainy Streets (13.2)
      - Miscellaneous - Rainy Streets (13.3)
      - Miscellaneous - Landscapes (13.4)
      - Miscellaneous - Landscapes (13.5)
      - Miscellaneous - City Scenes (13.6)
      - Miscellaneous - City Groups (13.7)
      - Miscellaneous - Architecture, medieval, circa 1959-1961 (13.8)
      - Miscellaneous - Packet including the Tricarico Save the Children Fund Nursery and unidentified shots, circa 1959-1961 (13.9)
      - Miscellaneous - including Tricarico and Gianna Thompson (13.10)
      - Miscellaneous - "Pix for N.Y. Times" (13.11)
      - Miscellaneous - "Pix for N.Y. Times" (13.12)
      - Miscellaneous - "Rejects" (9.11)
      - Miscellaneous - "Rejects" (9.12)
      - Miscellaneous - "Rejects" (9.13)
      - "George Deem Catalogue,", 1973 (9.18)
      - "George Deem Catalogue,", 1973 (9.19)
      - "George Deem Catalogue,", 1973 (9.20)
      - Miscellaneous - Color Snaps (13.13)
      - Miscellaneous, 1964 (13.14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974 (13.15)
      - Miscellaneous (13.16)
      - Miscellaneous (13.17)
      - Miscellaneous (13.18)
      - Miscellaneous (13.19)
      - Miscellaneous (13.20)
      - Miscellaneous (13.21)
      - Miscellaneous (13.22)
      - Miscellaneous (13.23)
      - Miscellaneous (13.24)
      - Miscellaneous (13.25)
      - Miscellaneous (13.26)
      - Miscellaneous (13.27)
      - Miscellaneous (13.28)
      - Miscellaneous (13.29)
      - Miscellaneous (9.14)
      - Miscellaneous (9.15)
      - Miscellaneous (9.16)
      - Miscellaneous (9.17)
      - Miscellaneous prints from negative envelopes — [no. 203] (13.30)
      - Miscellaneous prints from negative envelopes — [no. 206] (13.31)
      - Miscellaneous prints from negative envelopes — [no. 286] (13.32)
      - Miscellaneous prints from negative envelopes — [no. 332] (13.33)
      - Miscellaneous prints from negative envelopes — [no. 332] (13.34)
      - Miscellaneous prints from negative envelopes — [no. 335] (13.34)
      - Large prints used in Women of the Shadows (22.6)
      - Large prints used in Women of the Shadows (22.7)
      - Large prints removed from album, nos. 1-5 (22.8)
      - Large prints removed from album, nos. 6-10 (22.9)
      - Large prints removed from album, nos. 11-15 (22.10)
      - Large prints removed from album, nos. 16-20 (22.11)
      - Large prints removed from album, nos. 21-25 (22.12)
      - Large prints removed from album, nos. 26-30 (22.13)
      - Large prints removed from album, nos. 31-35 (22.14)
      - Large prints removed from album, nos. 36-38 (22.15)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.16)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.17)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.18)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.19)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.20)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.21)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.22)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.23)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.24)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.25)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.26)
      - Miscellaneous large prints (22.27)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (four 15x11 prints) (Box 24)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (one 6x9, one 11x11, and three 15x11 prints) (Box 25)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (two 10x15, one 9.5x14, two 11x15 and one 9x14 prints) (Box 26)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (two 10x15, one 11x13, one 9x13, one 11x15, and one 6.5x11 print) (Box 27)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (six 10x15 prints) (Box 28)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (two 23x19, and two 15x11prints) (Box 30)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (one 25.25x19.25 print) (Box 31)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (one 25.25x19.25 print) (Box 32)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (one 25.25x19.25 print) (Box 33)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (one 25.25x19.25 print) (Box 34)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (one 25.25x19.25 print) (Box 35)
      - 1971 exhibit prints, (one 25.25x19.25 print) (Box 36)
  - Negatives
    - Paper tags removed from original negative envelopes (F. 50.7)
    - "no. 1" (F. 37.1 - 37.4)
    - "no. 2" (F. 37.5 - 37.8)
    - "no. 3" (F. 37.9 - 37.12)
    - "no. 4" (F. 37.13 - 37.19)
    - "no. 5" (F. 37.20 - 37.25)
    - "no. 6" (F. 37.26 - 37.32)
    - "no. 7" (F. 37.33 - 37.39)
    - "no. 8 — Time-Life-Beckwith" (F. 37.40-37.46)
    - "no. 9" (F. 37.47-37.52)
    - "no. 10" (F. 37.53-37.59)
    - "no. 11" (F. 37.60-37.65)
    - "no. 12" (F. 37.66-37.71)
    - "no. 13" (F. 37.72-37.77)
    - "no. 14" (F. 37.78-37.83)
    - "no. 15" (F. 37.85-37.87)
    - "no. 16 — Time" (F. 37.88-37.90)
    - "no. 17 — Time" (F. 37.91-37.96)
    - "no. 18 — Time" (F. 37.97-37.102)
    - "no. 19 — Time" (F. 37.103-37.107)
    - "no. 20 — Time" (F. 37.108-37.113)
    - "no. 21 — Time" (F. 37.114-37.119)
    - "no. 22 — Time" (F. 37.120-37.125)
    - "no. 23 — Time" (F. 37.126-37.131)
    - "no. 24 — Time Life" (F. 38.1-38.6)
    - "no. 25 — Time Life" (F. 38.7-38.12)
    - "no. 26 — Beckwi[t]h" (F. 38.13-38.18)
    - "no. 27" (F. 38.19-38.24)
    - "no. 28" (F. 38.25-38.30)
    - "no. 29" (F. 38.31-38.36)
    - "no. 30" (F. 38.37-38.42)
    - "no. 31" (F. 38.43-38.48)
    - "no. 32" (F. 38.49-38.54)
    - "no. 33" (F. 38.55-38.60)
    - "no. 34" (F. 38.61-38.66)
    - "no. 35 — Life 4" (F. 38.67-38.72)
    - "no. 36 — Life 5" (F. 38.73-38.78)
    - "no. 37 — Time Life 2" (F. 38.79-38.84)
    - "no. 38 — Life 4" (F. 38.85-38.90)
    - "no. 39 — Life 8" (F. 38.91-38.96)
    - "no. 40 — Time Life 3" (F. 38.97-38.102)
    - "no. 41 — Life 2" (F. 38.103-38.108)
    - "no. 42 — Time Life 1" (F. 38.109-38.114)
    - "no. 43 — Life 6" (F. 38.115-38.120)
    - "no. 44 — Life 2" (F. 38.121-38.126)
    - "no. 45 — Life 3" (F. 38.127-38.132)
    - "no. 46 — Time Life" (F. 38.133-38.138)
    - "no. 47 — Time Life 2" (F. 38.139-38.144)
    - "no. 48 — Time Life 1" (F. 39.1-39.6)
    - "no. 49 — TL2" (F. 39.7-39.12)
    - "no. 50 — Time Life 1" (F. 39.13-39.18)
    - "no. 51" (F. 39.19-39.24)
    - "no. 52 — TL3" (F. 39.25-39.29)
    - "no. 53 — Time Life 1" (F. 39.30-39.35)
    - "no. 54 — TL2" (F. 39.36-39.41)
    - "no. 55 — TL4" (F. 39.42-39.47)
    - "no. 56 — TL5" (F. 39.48-39.53)
    - "no. 57 — TL6" (F. 39.54-39.59)
    - "no. 58 — TL7" (F. 39.60-39.63)
    - "no. 59 — Ti L 3" (F. 39.64-39.66)
    - "no. 60 — Time Life" (F. 39.67-39.69)
    - "no. 61" (F. 39.70-39.76)
    - "no. 62" (F. 39.77-39.83)
    - "no. 63 — Time" (F. 39.84-39.88)
    - "no. 64 — Li Time" (F. 39.89-39.94)
    - "no. 65 — 2 Time" (F. 39.95-39.100)
    - "no. 66 — 3 Time" (F. 39.101-39.105)
    - "no. 67 — Time" (F. 39.106-39.111)
    - "no. 68 — 1 Time" (F. 39.112-39.117)
    - "no. 69 — 8 Time" (F. 39.118-39.121)
    - "no. 70 — Cornelisi" (F. 39.122-39.127)
    - "no. 71 — Cornelisi" (F. 39.128-39.123)
    - "no. 72 — Cornelisi" (F. 39.124-39.128)
    - "no. 73 — 1 Cornelisa" (F. 40.1-40.6)
    - "no. 74 — Cornelisa" (F. 40.7-40.12)
    - "no. 75 — Cornelisi" (F. 40.13-40.18)
    - "no. 76 — Cornelisen" (F. 40.19-40.22)
    - "no. 76 — Rolei Negs Naples, Life- Cook Books, No contacts" (F. 40.23)
    - "no. 76 — 1 Time Life" (F. 40.24-40.26)
    - "no. 76 — 2 Time Life" (F. 40.27-40.29)
    - "no. 76 — 3 Time Life" (F. 40.30-40.32)
    - "no. 76 — 4 Time Life" (F. 40.33-40.35)
    - "no. 76 — 5 Time Life" (F. 40.36-40.38)
    - "no. 76 — 6 Time Life" (F. 40.39-40.41)
    - "no. 76 — 7 Time Life" (F. 40.42-40.44)
    - "no. 77 — Time Life" (F. 40.45-40.50)
    - "no. 78 — Cornelisen" (F. 40.51-40.56)
    - "no. 79 — Cornelisen" (F. 40.57-40.62)
    - "no. 80 — Cornelisen" (F. 40.63-40.68)
    - "no. 81 — Cornelisen" (F. 40.69-40.74)
    - "no. 82 — Cornelisen" (F. 40.75-40.78)
    - "no. 83 — Cornelisen" (F. 40.79-40.84)
    - "no. 84 — Provino Sent Wendy" (F. 40.85-40.88)
    - [no. 85] (F. 40.89-40.92)
    - "no. 86" (F. 40.93-40.96)
    - "no. 87" (F. 40.97-40.102)
    - "no. 88" (F. 40.103-40.106)
    - "no. 89" (F. 40.107-40.110)
    - "no. 90" (F. 40.111-40.114)
    - "no. 91" (F. 40.115-40.119)
    - "no. 92 — 1 Cornelisen" (F. 40.120-40.125)
    - "no. 93 — 2 Cornelisen" (F. 40.126-40.131)
    - "no. 94" (F. 40.132-40.139)
    - "no. 95 — 5" (F. 41.1-41.8)
    - "no. 96 — 3" (F. 41.9-41.16)
    - "no. 97 — 6" (F. 41.17-41.24)
    - "no. 98 — 8" (F. 41.25-41.32)
    - "no. 99 — 9" (F. 41.33-41.39)
    - "no. 100 — 7" (F. 41.40-41.47)
    - "no. 101" (F. 41.48-41.53)
    - "no. 102 — "Cornelisen" (F. 41.54-41.61)
    - "no. 103" (F. 41.62-41.67)
    - "no. 104 — Time 2" (F. 41.68-41.73)
    - "no. 105 — Time 1" (F. 41.74-41.77)
    - "no. 106 — Cornelisen 1 4a W. of S." (F. 41.78-41.81)
    - "no. 107 — Cornelisen 2" (F. 41.82-41.87)
    - "no. 108 — Cornelisen 3" (F. 41.88-41.93)
    - "no. 109 — Cornelisen 4" (F. 41.94-41.98)
    - "no. 110 — Cornelisen 2" (F. 41.99-41.104)
    - "no. 111 — Cornelisen 1" (F. 41.105-41.109)
    - "no. 112 — Cornelisen 1" (F. 41.110-41.115)
    - "no. 113 — Cornelisen 2" (F. 41.116-41.120)
    - "no. 114 — 5 Italy 8520" (F. 41.121-41.126)
    - "no. 115 — Cornelisen #3 #8" (F. 41.127-41.132)
    - "no. 116 — Cornelisen, Conir Sejuator #10A-11, "#18A-19, 33A, 35A" (F. 41.133-41.138)
    - "no. 117 — M.Y" (F. 42.1-42.3)
    - "no. 118 — Cornelisen" (F. 42.4-42.9)
    - "no. 119 — c" (F. 42.10 -13)
    - "no. 120 — Cornelisen" (F. 42.14-42.19)
    - "no. 121 — c" (F. 42.20-42.25)
    - "no. 122 — Italy 11 8520" (F. 42.26-42.28)
    - "no. 123 — c" (F. 42.29-42.34)
    - "no. 124 — 2 Italy 8520" (F. 42.35-42.40)
    - "no. 125 — 6 Italy 8520" (F. 42.41-42.46)
    - "no. 126 — 8520 Mezzogiovni 1A" (F. 42.47-42.51)
    - "no. 127 — 9 Italy 8520" (F. 42.52-42.57)
    - "no. 128 — Italy 10 8520" (F. 42.58-42.63)
    - "no. 129 — 4 Italy 8520" (F. 42.64-42.69)
    - "no. 130 — 8 Italy 8520" (F. 42.70-42.71)
    - "no. 131 — c" (F. 42.72-42.75)
    - "no. 132 — Italy 7 8520" (F. 42.76-42.83)
    - "no. 133 — 3 Italy 8520" (F. 42.84-42.89)
    - "no. 134" (F. 42.90-42.95)
    - "no. 135" (F. 42.96-42.98)
    - "no. 136" (F. 42.99-42.102)
    - [no. 137 empty]
    - "no. 138" (F. 42.103-42.107)
    - "no. 139" (F. 42.109-42.112)
    - "no. 140" (F. 42.113-42.118)
    - "no. 141 —#3" (F. 42.119-42.127)
    - "no. 142" (F. 42.128-42.133)
    - "no. 143" (F. 43.1-43.8)
    - "no. 144" (F. 43.9-43.15)
    - "no. 145" (F. 43.16-43.21)
    - "no. 146" (F. 43.22-43.28)
    - "no. 147 — Cornelisen 1" (F. 43.29-43.34)
    - "no. 148 — C5" (F. 43.35-43.38)
    - "no. 149 — C2" (F. 43.39-43.44)
    - "no. 150 — B" (F. 43.45-43.51)
    - "no. 151 — 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 2 7x10" (F. 43.52-43.57)
    - "no. 152 — A" (F. 43.58-43.63)
    - "no. 153 — 15a-1b, 21, 22, 29, 30, 31, 19" (F. 43.64-43.68)
    - "no. 154" (F. 43.69-43.75)
    - "no. 155 — C3" (F. 43.76-43.81)
    - "no. 156 — C4" (F. 43.82-43.87)
    - "no. 157" (F. 43.88-43.95)
    - "no. 158" (F. 43.96-43.103)
    - "no. 159" (F. 43.104-43.109)
    - "no. 160 — Cornelisen 1, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 43.110-43.115)
    - "no. 161 — C2, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 43.116-43.121)
    - "no. 162 — C3, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 43.122-43.127)
    - "no. 163 — C4, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 43.128-43.133)
    - "no. 164 — C5, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 43.134-43.139)
    - "no. 165 — C6, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 44.1-44.6)
    - "no. 166 — C, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 44.7-44.12)
    - "no. 167 — C8, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 44.13-44.18)
    - "no. 168 — C, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 44.19-44.22)
    - "no. 169 — C, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 44.23-44.28)
    - "no. 170 — C, Rehearsals 1975" (F. 44.29-44.34)
    - "no. 171" (F. 44.35-44.38)
    - "no. 172" (F. 44.39-44.42)
    - "no. 173" (F. 44.43-44.48)
    - "no. 174" (F. 44.49-44.52)
    - "no. 175" (F. 44.53-44.57)
    - [no. 176] — "Negs House C" (F. 44.58-44.61)
    - [no. 177] — "Negs House C" (F. 44.62-44.67)
    - [no. 178] — "Negs House C" (F. 44.68-44.71)
    - [no. 179] — "Negs House C" (F. 44.72-44.77)
    - [no. 180] — "Negs House C" (F. 44.78-44.81)
    - [no. 181] — "Negs House C" (F. 44.82-44.87)
    - [no. 182] — "Abruzzo-Peg 1966 TL. (Beckwith) A" (F. 44.88-44.90)
    - [no. 183] — "Ortona - Spring 67 Color" (F. 44.91-44.94)
    - [no. 184] (F. 44.95-44.107)
    - [no. 185] — "Miss Beckwith (Life)" (F. 44.108-44.111)
    - [no. 186] — "[Gaizano?] - Scandale '62 (F. 44.112-44.116)
    - [no. 187] — "2 copie di Tricarico [Wi]Berg [?]" (F. 44.117-44.122)
    - [no. 188] — "Tricarico Costumes Sept. 1960, Costumes Tricarico 3-60" (F. 44.123-44.127)
    - [no. 189] — "Chieti Foundling Home March 1960" (F. 44.128-44.130)
    - [no. 190] — "Festa-T-‘64" (F. 44.131-44.135)
    - [no. 191] — "Festa ’64 T 1" (F. 45.1-45.4)
    - [no. 192] — "Tricarico Gen. Oct 1969" (F. 45.5-45.10)
    - [no. 193] — "4" [Tricarico Apr. 1963] (F. 45.11-45.15)
    - [no. 194] — "2 Tricarico Ap. ‘63" (F. 45.16-45.23)
    - [no. 195] — "3 Tricarico Ap. 63" (F. 45.24-45.30)
    - [no. 196] — "Tricarico…" [1959] (F. 45.31-45.36)
    - [no. 197] — "5" [Tricarico Apr. 1963] (F. 45.37-45.41)
    - [no. 198] — "1 Tricarico Ap ‘63" (F. 45.42-45.43)
    - [no. 199] — "Tricarico 196" (F. 45.44-45.50)
    - [no. 200] — "Puh. Pck S.and P. 1979" (F. 45.51-45.60)
    - [no. 201] — "Cornelisen 980" (F. 45.61-45.63)
    - [no. 202] — "Cornelisen 950" (F. 45.64)
    - [no. 203] — "2550" (F. 45.65-45.67)
    - [no. 204] — "Cornelisen" (F. 45.68-45.70)
    - [no. 205] (F. 45.71-45.73)
    - [no. 206] — "Cornelisen" (F. 45.74-45.76)
    - [no. 207] — "South" (F. 45.77-45.79)
    - [no. 208] (F. 45.80-45.81)
    - [no. 209] — "Snows and Ortona Bits [?]" (F. 45.82-45.85)
    - [no. 210] — "San Tomaso 1956 - Ortona" (F. 45.86-45.87)
    - [no. 211] — "Terrace 21A '64" (F. 45.88-45.90)
    - [no. 212] — "Tricarico '66 Night Tower" (F. 45.91-45.94)
    - [no. 213] — "Greece '64 - Rocca simbalda - color print" (F. 45.95-45.98)
    - [no. 214] — "Snows '56 [?]" (F. 45.99)
    - [no. 215] — "Martha P. - Some [?] Tower" (F. 45.100-45.102)
    - [no. 216] — "Tricarico '63" (F. 45.103-45.104)
    - [no. 217] — "Tricarico '66" (F. 45.105-45.108)
    - [no. 218] — "Tricarico '66" (F. 45.109-45.110)
    - [no. 219] (F. 45.111-45.114)
    - [no. 220] — "Tricarico Procerdias [?] 1959-1960" (F. 45.115-45.118)
    - [no. 221] — "Calabria 1956" (F. 45.119-45.122)
    - [no. 222] — "Sanjenico 1956" (F. 45.123-45.125)
    - [no. 223] — "Lucania 1956; Hosp. [?] 1961" (F. 45.126-45.128)
    - [no. 224] — "Rocconova 1959" (F. 46.1-46.4)
    - [no. 225] — "Tricarico Corei 1959-1960" (F. 46.5-46.12)
    - [no. 226] — "Tricarico Festival and General 35mm" (F. 46.13-46.16)
    - [no. 227] — "Tricarico Feb. 1961" (F. 46.17-46.20)
    - [no. 228] — "Tricarico 1960" (F. 46.21-46.24)
    - [no. 229] — "Rocca Imperial- [?] 1960" (F. 46.25-46.27)
    - [no. 230] — "City - Matera" (F. 46.28-46.31)
    - [no. 231] — "[L- ?] 1956" (F. 46.32-46.35)
    - [no. 232] — "Alianello - 1960" (F. 46.36-46.38)
    - [no. 233] — "Sig. Thompson £600, Tricarico - June 1959" (F. 46.39-46.40)
    - [no. 234] — "Stigliano - San Marino - Forte - Alianello" (F. 46.41-46.43)
    - [no. 235] — "Children [?] Sr. [?] Tricarico 1960" (F. 46.44-46.45)
    - [no. 236] — "Tricarico Lady A. 1956" (F. 46.46-46.49)
    - [no. 237] — "Tricarico - Spolero Fall '62" (F. 46.50-46.53)
    - [no. 238] — "Alianello 1960" (F. 46.54-46.57)
    - [no. 239] — "Alianello 1960" (F. 46.58-46.61)
    - [no. 240] — "Greek [?] [?]" (F. 46.62-46.65)
    - [no. 241] — "Odds Lucania - Puglia" (F. 46.66-46.69)
    - [no. 242] — "Matera - General" (F. 46.70-46.73)
    - [no. 243] — "General Building" (F. 46.74-46.76)
    - [no. 244] — "Porto freo '63" (F. 46.77-46.80)
    - [no. 245] — "[?] [?] Ortona Personal" (F. 46.81-46.82)
    - [no. 246] — "Gargave 1956" (F. 46.83-46.86)
    - [no. 247] — "[?] [?] 1962" (F. 46.87-46.90)
    - [no. 248] — "Savelletri [?] '62" (F. 46.91-46.94)
    - [no. 249] — "Ciura 1954" (F. 46.95-46.98)
    - [no. 250] — "Chieti Foundling Home 1960" (F. 46.99-46.100)
    - [no. 251] — "[S- ?] Grei" (F. 46.101-46.102)
    - [no. 252] — "Tricarico Nov. 1962" (F. 46.103-46.106)
    - [no. 253] — "Tricarico Nursery" (F. 46.107-46.110)
    - [no. 254] — "Chieti Foundling Home 1960" (F. 46.111 -114)
    - [no. 255] — "Chieti Foundling Home 1960" (F. 46.115-46.118)
    - [no. 256] — "Tricarico '66" (F. 46.119-46.122)
    - [no. 257] — "Rome R. N. C. Cornelisen 950" (F. 47.1-47.2)
    - [no. 258] — "Tricarico 66 Women- Landsc." (F. 47.3-47.6)
    - [no. 259] — "Portofino May '63" (F. 47.7-47.10)
    - [no. 260] — "Tricarico (and Orleans and Caleoglie) Oct. Nov. 1960" (F. 47.11-47.14)
    - [no. 261] — "Trevene Berugia" (F. 47.15-47.16)
    - [no. 262] — "Portofino 63" (F. 47.17-47.20)
    - [no. 263] — "[C- ?] Building" (F. 47.21-47.24)
    - [no. 264] — "[M- ?] [G- ?] 1961" (F. 47. 25-47.28)
    - [no. 265] — "Color Rwc Yrc Rowe" (F. 47.29-47.30)
    - [no. 266] — "Ortona-Nina 1961" (F. 47.31-47.33)
    - [no. 267] — "Alicueo Bay 1960" (F. 47.34-47.37)
    - [no. 268] — "Ezzito 1960 Albano Stigilano Alcaiuo" (F. 47.38-47.39)
    - [no. 269] — "Tricarico Children" (F. 47.40-47.43)
    - [no. 270] — "Tricarico- Colreo 1961" (F. 47.44-47.47)
    - [no. 271] — "Corleto-Perticara 1961" (F. 47.48-47.51)
    - [no. 272] — "Salavelra 1956" (F. 47.52-47.54)
    - [no. 273] — "Salavelra 1956" (F. 47.55-47.57)
    - [no. 274] — "Matera General" (F. 47.58-47.61)
    - [no. 275] — "Pers- Dec. 1960" (F. 47.62-47.65)
    - [no. 276] (F. 47.66-47.69)
    - [no. 277] — "Tricarico ’66 M[?]" (F. 47.70-47.72)
    - [no. 278] — "Tricarico ‘66" (F. 47.73-47.76)
    - [no. 279] — "Tricarico ’66 Moving" (F. 47.77-47.79)
    - [no. 280] — "Tricarico Fall ‘66" (F. 47.80-47.83)
    - [no. 281] — "Tricarico Fall ‘66" (F. 47.84-47.85)
    - [no. 282] — "Tricarico Fall ‘66" (F. 47.86-47.89)
    - [no. 283] (F. 47.90-47.93)
    - [no. 284 empty]
    - [no. 285] — "Peg F. Peylier" (F. 47.94-47.97)
    - [no. 286] — "Sardinia" (F. 47.98-47.99)
    - [no. 287] (F. 47.100-47.103)
    - [no. 288] — "Ezzito 1960" (F. 47.104-47.107)
    - [no. 289] — "Scandale and Eeu. Mareli 1960" (F. 47.108-47.114)
    - [no. 290] — "Ezzito - Farneta Aug. 1960" (F. 47.115-118)
    - [no. 291] — "Ezzito - Farnetta Aug. 1960" (F. 48.1-48.4)
    - [no. 292] — "Ezzito - Farneta Aug. 1960" (F. 48.5-48.8)
    - [no. 293] — "Trani ‘63" (F. 48.9-48.10)
    - [no. 294] — "Scandale - May 1961" (F. 48.11-48.15)
    - [no. 295] — "Ezzito 1960 - Farneta" (F. 48.16-48.19)
    - [no. 296] — "Scandale 62" (F. 48.20-48.23)
    - [no. 297] — "Calabria [C- ?]" (F. 48.24-48.26)
    - [no. 298] — "Odds South (Fareuta, Ezzito, Pont Power, Maut Albano etc.) Aug 1960" (F. 48.27-48.28)
    - [no. 299] — "Tricarico- Children [C- ?] 1960" (F. 48.29-48.32)
    - [no. 300] (F. 48.33-48.37)
    - [no. 301] (F. 48.38-48.42)
    - [no. 302] (F. 48.43-48.50)
    - [no. 303] (F. 48.51-48.54)
    - [no. 304] — "Tricarico Cren. 1959-60 Specials" (F. 48.55-48.59)
    - [no. 305] — "Tricarico Nov. 1962" (F. 48.60-48.62)
    - [no. 306] — "Civita 1954" (F. 48.63-48.65)
    - [no. 307] — "Civita 1954" (F. 48.66-48.69)
    - [no. 308] — "Civita [?] 1955" (F. 48.70-48.71)
    - [no. 309] — "Greece-Turkey" (F. 48.72-48.76)
    - [no. 310] — "Rome" (F. 48.77-48.80)
    - [no. 311] — "Rome 4rc Rwe Acc" (F. 48.81-48.84)
    - [no. 312] — "Tolve Feitei ‘64" (F. 48.85-48.88)
    - [no. 313] — "Tricarico frei." (F. 48.89-48.92)
    - [no. 314] — "Tricarico Coreii 1959-1960" (F. 48.93-48.96)
    - [no. 315] — "Tricarico Corn. 1960 -1989" (F. 48.99-48.102)
    - [no. 316] — "Barbetta ‘63" (F. 48.103-48.106)
    - [no. 317] — "Summer ‘63" (F. 48.107-48.110)
    - [no. 318] — "Apr V [B- ?] 1962" (F. 48.111-48.114)
    - [no. 319] — "Nursery Tricarico 1961" (F. 48.115-48.118)
    - [no. 320] — "Christmas Tricarico 1960" (F. 49.1-49.4)
    - [no. 321] — "Tricarico Children 1960" (F. 49.5-49.8)
    - [no. 322] — "Tricarico Nursery 1960" (F. 49.9-49.12)
    - [no. 323] — "Wells Cathedral 1960" (F. 49.13-49.16)
    - [no. 324] — "Ostia Gen. 162" (F. 49.17-49.20)
    - [no. 325] — "Sardyua April 1961" (F. 49.21-49.24)
    - [no. 326] — "pers" (F. 49.25)
    - [no. 327] — "self-portraits July 1960 Dec. 1960" (F. 49.26-49.27)
    - [no. 328] — "Jan. ’62 [Nice ?]" (F. 49.28-49.31)
    - [no. 329] — "Calabria Odds-" (F. 49.32-49.34)
    - [no. 330] — "Scandale ‘62" (F. 49.35-49.38)
    - [no. 331] (F. 49.39-49.40)
    - [no. 332] (F. 49.41-49.49)
    - [no. 333] (F. 49.50-49.54)
    - [no. 334] — "Tricarico ‘63" (F. 49.55-49.58)
    - [no. 335] (F. 49.59-49.62)
    - [no. 336] (F. 49.63-49.65)
    - [no. 337] (F. 49.66-49.70)
    - [no. 338] (F. 49.71-49.80)
    - [no. 339] (F. 49.81)
    - [no. 340] (F. 49.82-49.83)
    - [no. 341] (F. 49.84-49.86)
    - [no. 342] (F. 50.1 -50.2)
    - [no. 343] (F. 50.3 -50.5)
    - [no. 344] (F. 50.6)
  - Contact Sheets and Contact Prints
    - Contact Sheets
      - Photo shoot of A.C. (14.1)
      - "nos. 1-10" (14.2)
      - "nos. 11-20" (14.3)
      - "nos. 21-30" (14.4)
      - "nos. 31-40" (14.5)
      - "nos. 41-50" (14.6)
      - "nos. 51-60" (14.7)
      - "nos. 61-70" (14.8)
      - "nos. 71-80" (14.9)
      - "nos. 81-90" (14.10)
      - "nos. 91-100" (14.11)
      - "nos. 101-110" (14.12)
      - "nos. 111-120" (14.13)